

Simon Hyltegård Github Portfolio +46721744454 simon. home@hotmail.com

Software

Unity3DVSMayaDirectXZbrush

Programming/Scripting (Advanced)

○ C ○ C++

Programming/Scripting (Intermediate)

o Python o Java

Programming/Scripting (Basic)

JavaScriptMELGit Bash

o Lua

Simon Hyltegård

Technical Artist

About me Technical Artist focused on front-end development with 8 years experience in Unity3D and an early starting career using *Warcraft3*'s World Editor. A strong desire to get started creating games after school lead to running a game company under Blekinge Business Incubator, with one released game. A background working in newly started companies and small teams has made me delve and take interests in many different areas of development, striving when I can learn new things and keep several balls in the air.

Experience

2018 - Today, Technical Artist at Attractive Interactive

Developing the mobile game *Paper Game* as a Technical Artist/Front-End programmer. Being a trick of all trades with a focus on UI-systems, gameplay logic and in-engine tools.

2017 - 2018, Artist at Loophole Interactive

Ran a game company where I worked mainly with 3D-modelling, rigging and animation. Released the PC-game *King of The Couch: Zoovival* and later on travelled to San Francisco to pitch the game *Boss Forge* for investors.

March 2016 - June 2016, Bachelor's Thesis in Digital Game Development

Two Anti-aliasing Methods for Creating a Uniform Look

A thesis for applying anti-aliasing for different rendering elements while keeping a uniform look.

October 2015 - March 2016, Game Engine

Game engine using DirectX. Integrated Autodesk Maya to render its viewport inside the engine using circle buffer.

Education

2013 - 2016, Technical Artist (172.5hp)

- 37.5hp Programming courses
- 22.5hp Scripting courses

2010-2013, **Technology Program**, Österänggymnasiet, Kristianstad Introduced to Java programming and working parallelly with Javascript during leisure.

References

References upon request.